{
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "A pre-trip inspection should be completed.",
            "options": [
                "at least once a week.",
                "if any problems occurred the last the time the vehicle was operated.",
                "before operating the vehicle."
            ],
            "correctAnswer": 3
        },
        {
            "question": "What should you do when you are driving at night?",
            "options": [
                "Make sure you are driving slow enough so you can stop within the range of your headlights in an emergency.",
                "Roll down your window so that the fresh air will help keep you awake.",
                "If you are sleepy, drink coffee or other caffeine products."
            ],
            "correctAnswer": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Which of the following is the correct term for a long commercial vehicle's tendency to swing wide on turns?",
            "options": [
                "Sidetracking.",
                "Offtracking.",
                "Fishtailing."
            ],
            "correctAnswer": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "When a coolant container is part of a pressurized system, you can",
            "options": [
                "check the coolant level of a hot engine.",
                "safely remove the radiator cap and add coolant while the engine is hot.",
                "use water only in the cooling system."
            ],
            "correctAnswer": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "When you are parked at the side of the road at night, you must:",
            "options": [
                "warn others by turning on your 4-way emergency flashers.",
                "put your warning devices out within 15 minutes.",
                "use your left turn signal lights to give warning to other drivers."
            ],
            "correctAnswer": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "While doing the pre-trip inspection on your vehicleâ€™s steering and exhaust system you found the following problems. Which one, if any, should be fixed before you drive the vehicle?",
            "options": [
                "Too many vertical stacks.",
                "Oil on the tie rod. ",
                "Play in the steering wheel of more than 10 degrees (2 inches on a 20-inch steering wheel)."
            ],
            "correctAnswer": 3
        }
        ,
        {
            "question": "Containerized loads",
            "options": [
                "are exempt from hazardous materials restrictions.",
               "are exempt from weight limit restrictions.",
                "generally are used when freight is carried part way by rail or ship."
                
            ],
            "correctAnswer": 3
        }
        ,
        {
            "question": "You are exiting a highway using an offramp that curves downhill and you are driving a heavy vehicle. You should:",
            "options": [
                "do nothing because the posted speed limit for the offramp is usually 10 miles per hour below the safe speed limit for the offramp.",
                "slow to a safe speed before the curve. ",
                "downshift after you are in the curve."
            ],
            "correctAnswer": 2
        }
        ,
        {
            "question": "Water can safely be used on which of these fires?",
            "options": [
                "Electrical.",
                "Gasoline.",
                "Neither of the above. "
                
            ],
            "correctAnswer": 3
        }
        ,
        {
            "question": "Three things add up to the total stopping distance for your vehicle. They are:",
            "options": [
                "perception distance, reaction distance, braking distance.",
                "observation distance, reaction distance, slowing distance. ",
                "perception distance, response distance, reaction distance."
            ],
            "correctAnswer": 1
        }

    ]
}